准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
粉红小偷
分镜总监
编剧
翻译: 1440kHz
技术总监
动画总监
制片指导
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
水母田
跟你说  派大星
You know, Patrick
我全年最爱的时节就是水母大迁徙
the jellyfish migration is my favorite time of year
整整三天
For three whole days
全世界的水母都会聚到一处
jellyfish from around the globe gather on one spot
分享水母的小秘密
to trade jelly secrets
派大星  你看
Patrick, look
蓝冠爆爆水母
A blue-crested blaster
从来没见过这种水母  太稀有了
I've never seen one before, they're really rare
斑点喷喷水母
And a speckled squirter
双拳跳跳水母
A two-fisted jumper
金嗓子刺刺水母
And a golden-throated stinger
今年的大迁徙一定特别盛大
This year's migration is gonna be a big one
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob?
看来得出动可靠好朋友了
This looks like a job for ol' reliable
可靠好朋友
公交站
今天真是最美好的捉水母日
That was the most beautiful day of jellyfishing ever
我的破网一只都没捉到
Well, I didn't catch a thing with my dumb old net
幸好我有可靠好朋友
Lucky for me, I have ol' reliable
碳纤维网柄
Carbon-fiber handle
钛合金网体  人体工学硅胶握把
titanium-alloy netting
and form-fitting silicone grips
没错
Yes, sir
可靠好朋友是世上最厉害的网
Ol' reliable is the best net in the world
我宁可拼了命都要那样的网
I would kill for a net like that
像是拼了萝卜这种小东西了命
Yeah, somethin' small, like a carrot
蜘蛛不行  看着难受
But not spiders, they're icky
晚安  派大星
Good-night, Patrick
晚安  海绵宝宝
Good-night, SpongeBob
我爱捉水母
I love jellyfishing
准备好迎接水母大迁徙的第二天啦
Time to get ready
for day two of the jellyfish migration
先拿出我可靠的水母网  可靠好朋友
And I'll start
with my trusty jellyfishing net, old reliable
可靠好朋友
Ol' reliable?
它不见了
It's gone
啊对  裤子
Oh, right, pants
穿了一条裤子后
派大星  可靠好朋友被偷走了
Patrick, ol' reliable's been stolen
可靠好朋友失窃
往那边贴一张  派大星
Put one over there, Patrick
贴完了
I'm all done
可能应该再传开一点点
Maybe we should spread out a little
裤头村报
可靠好朋友失窃
水母大迁徙
快报
Flash
精彩的水母大迁徙已经进入第二天
The jellyfish migration
enters its second day of fantastic jellyfishing
第二天
现在连线现场记者了解情况
We now go live to our reporter on the scene
今年的迁徙规模为本世纪最大
This year's migration is the largest in a century
我很同情某些
I feel truly sorry
这场盛会哪怕错过了一分钟的可怜虫
for the poor saps who will miss
even one minute of this remarkable event
请注意  裤头村
Attention, Bikini Bottom
我的水母网被偷了
My jellyfishing net has been stolen
只要完好无损归还  将有巨额奖赏
I am prepared to offer a large reward
for its safe return
奖赏
Reward?
总共有多少
How much we talkin' about?
十二块  还有
$12 and
两块  十块
two, 10
二十块
twenty
三毛八
38 cents
我来搞定
I'm on the case
虽然今天新闻少  你们也别这样
Guys, I know it's a slow news day, but come on
喂  喂
Hello, hello
海绵宝宝  网找回来了吗
SpongeBob, did you get your net back?
赶紧挂了  派大星
Get off the line, Patrick
可能会有谁打电话
Someone might be trying to call
提供可靠好朋友的线索
about ol' reliable
抱歉
Sorry
网找回来了吗
Did you get your net yet?
没有  派大星
No, Patrick
没找到我的网就别打电话
don't call unless you found my net
喂
Hello?
海绵宝宝  找到你的网了
SpongeBob, I found your net
什么
What
真的吗  派大星
really, Patrick?
不完全真
Not really
我只是有点寂寞了
I just got lonely
这下我网再也找不回来了
I'll never get my net back
可靠好朋友彻底丢了  只能认命了
I'll just have to accept
that ol' reliable is gone forever
派大星运气真好
Patrick's lucky
大半夜还能用自己的水母网捉水母
Gets to practice in the middle of the night
with his jellyfishing net
奇怪的是  派大星的网昨天就散架了
Funny thing is, Patrick's net disintegrated yesterday
海绵宝宝  可靠好朋友找回来了吗
SpongeBob, did you get ol' reliable back yet?
还没找到
No, not yet
派大星  要是你偷了我的水母网
Hey, Patrick, wouldn't it be the funniest thing
岂不是太搞笑了
if you had taken my jellyfish net?
不会
No
确实  那样就太傻了
Yeah, that would be silly
想起来了  我要送你个礼物
That reminds me, I got you a present
什么礼物
A present, what is it?
是坦白熊
It's a confess-a-bear
可以把所有秘密告诉这位特别的朋友
He's a special friend you tell all your secrets to
谢了  海绵宝宝
Thanks, SpongeBob
我先走了  你们两个慢慢聊
I'll just leave you two alone to get acquainted
我的名字是坦白熊
"My name is confess-a-bear"
向我说出你所有秘密吧
"Tell me all your secrets"
我最近做了件不那么光彩的事
I did something recently I'm not proud of
我不是故意要做的
I didn't mean to do it
反正就是发生了
It just sort of happened
也许你应该说说看
"Maybe you should talk about it"
可那还牵扯到我最好的朋友海绵宝宝
Well, it involves my best friend, SpongeBob
虽然他好像不知道  但
I don't think he knows what happened, but
要是他发现了  会很伤心的
It would really upset him if he found out
跟坦白熊说
"Tell confess-a-bear"
我已经说太多了
I've said too much, already
快跟坦白熊说
"Tell confess-a-bear now"
快
"Now"
我不小心把海绵宝宝的牙刷碰倒
I accidentally knocked SpongeBob's toothbrush
掉进了马桶里
into the toilet
然后我没洗就把它放回台上了
and then I put it back on the counter without washing it
坦白熊
Confess-a-bear?
你没对我生气吧  坦白熊
You're mad at me, aren't you, confess-a-bear?
派大星  我们得谈谈
Patrick, we need to talk
别进来
Don't come in
我没穿好衣服
I'm not decent
家里乱糟糟的
The house is a mess
有核泄漏
There's a radiation leak
派大星  你在哪
Patrick, where are you?
灯怎么给关了
Why are the lights off?
我在里面  马上就出来
I'm in here, be out in a second
可靠好朋友
Ol' reliable
你好
Hello
你手上是啥  派大星
What's in your hand, Patrick?
没什么
Nothing
另一只手呢
What's in your other hand?
我另一只手也没拿东西
Nothing in my other hand
我得走了
Well, I gotta go
好  再见
OK, bye
派大星不会偷可靠好朋友的
Patrick wouldn't steal ol' reliable
是吗
Would he?
我宁可拼了命也要那样的网
I would kill for a net like that
难道我最好的朋友一直是个江洋大盗
Have I been best friends with a master thief?
非弄清楚不可
I must know for sure
早安  派大星
Good morning, Patrick
早安  海绵宝宝
Morning, SpongeBob
你今天要干嘛  兄弟
What you gonna do today, buddy?
没干嘛
Nothing
那我去上班了  再见
Well, I'm off to work, see you later
再见
Bye
倒要来看看你怎么没干嘛  小毛贼
Now we'll just see what sort of nothing
you're really up to, Sneaky McSneakypants
八小时后
他可真厉害
He is good
要想真正了解某个家伙
You never really know a guy
得用高倍率望远镜盯他个八小时
until you've stared at him for eight hours
through high-powered binoculars
他哪去了
Where'd he go?
嗨  海绵宝宝
Hi, SpongeBob
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
你干嘛
What're you doing?
没干嘛
Nothin'
刚干完了
I just finished
待办事项单
没干嘛
快看
Hey, look
这里可以看到我刚站的地方
You can see where I was just standin' from here
天啊  你要是有什么打算
Boy, if you'd wanted to
完全就能整天在这里监视我
you could have spied on me all day from right here
很怪异吧
Creepy, huh?
总之你拿着这副望远镜干什么
Anyway, what are you doin' with those binoculars?
我没望远镜  看吧
I don't have any binoculars, see?
你表现很奇怪
You're acting weird
我才没表现很奇怪
I'm not acting weird
你表现才奇怪
You're acting weird
你
You're
表现
acting
很奇怪
weird
好  再见
OK, bye
你好  你谁啊
Hello, who are you?
你好  小伙子
Greetings, young fellow
我愿意花大价钱
I'm willing to pay top dollar
来买有着特殊意义的捉水母工具
for jellyfishing items with sentimental value
你应该懂我的意思吧
if you know what I mean
不懂
No
小道消息说  你知道要上哪去找
Word on the street is that you know where to get
高质量捉水母工具  对吧
quality jellyfishing supplies, hmm?
哪个道说的
What street said that?
这条道吗
Was it this one?
管好你自己的事
Mind your own business
派大星先生啊
Oh, Mr. Star
我知道你手上有个稀有水母网
I know that you are in possession
of a rare jellyfishing net
我愿意出十亿买下那张网
I will pay $1 billion for that net
虽然我不认识你
I don't know who you are
但我绝对不会把这个水母网给你
but you're not getting this jellyfishing net
就算你出一百万也不卖
I wouldn't sell it for a million dollars
一百也不卖
not for a $100
就算出一块我也不卖
I wouldn't even sell it for $1
真的
Really
就算出多少都不卖
You can't have it for any price
为什么
And why not?
这东西对我来说比钱重要多了
This means more to me than money
那可是我朋友海绵宝宝的
It's my friend SpongeBob's
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
谢天谢地你来了
Thank goodness you're here
有个可怕的八字胡男
There was a scary guy with a moustache
在问一大堆怪问题
asking a lot of weird questions
派大星  我就是那个可怕八字胡男
Patrick, I'm the scary moustache guy
海绵宝宝  为什么
Why, SpongeBob, why?
为什么要戴这么可怕的八字胡
Why would you wear such a scary moustache?
为什么要偷走我的水母网
Why did you steal my jellyfishing net?
什么
What?
我是你最好的朋友
I'm your best friend
你再也不是我最好的朋友了
You were my best friend
你这个偷水母网的坏小偷
you no-good jellyfishing net thief
你怎么能这么觉得
How could you think that?
因为你亲口说出来了
Because you said it
你说那是你朋友海绵宝宝的
You said it was your friend SpongeBob's
礼物
Gift
什么
What?
是我要给朋友海绵宝宝的礼物
It's my friend SpongeBob's gift
我给你做了个新网
I made you a new net
送给海绵宝宝
"For SpongeBob"
你给我做了个新水母网
You made me a new jellyfishing net?
你可真贴心
That is so thoughtful of you
派大星
Patrick?
你在干嘛  最好的朋友
What you doing, best friend?
我不是你最好的朋友
I'm not your best friend
我是个偷水母网的坏小偷
I'm a no-good jelly netting thief fish
你要去哪
Where are you going?
趁着还有尊严  离开裤头村
I'm leaving Bikini Bottom while I still have my dignity
派大星  不要
Patrick, no
公交站
我们情谊已尽了吗
So, this is it?
除非有什么意外
Barring the unforeseen hand of fate
恐怕是这样
I'm afraid it is
派大星  别走
Patrick, don't go
对不起我冤枉了你
I'm sorry I accused you
虽然丢了网已经够糟了
It's bad enough I lost my net
但我也不想丢了我最好的朋友
I don't want to lose my best friend, too
求你原谅我
Please forgive me
磨蹭什么啊
What's the hold up?
是你们俩啊
It's you two
看好  你又把网落在公交上了
Look, you left your net on the bus again
可靠好朋友
Old reliable?
我把你落在公交上了
I left you on the bus?
你每周都落公交上
You do it every week
还走不走了
Now, can we get going?
派大星  请你收下这个当作纪念
Patrick, I want you to take this to remember me by
你要把可靠好朋友送给我吗
You're giving me old reliable?
我接受你的道歉
I accept your apology
来吧  傻大个
Come here, you big lug
他们次次都这样
They do this all the time
我说真的
I'm serious
算了
Never mind
我要留在裤头村不走了
I'm staying in Bikini Bottom
万岁
Hooray
要去捉水母吗
You wanna go jellyfishing?
我刚有了个新网
I just got a new net
我也是
So did I
这可是我最好的朋友给我做的
My best friend made it for me
木偶章鱼哥
分镜总监
编剧
翻译: 1440kHz
技术总监
动画总监
制片指导
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
我就爱一觉睡到自然醒
I love waking up to my own circadian rhythm
而不是被闹钟叫醒
Without the aid of an alarm clock
早安  章鱼哥
Morning, Squidward
我按你说的  一直等到你睡醒哦
I waited for you to stop sleeping like you asked
今天白天有什么打算  章鱼哥
So you got any plans for the day, Squidward?
好吧  章鱼哥
OK, Squidward
等会再聊
I'll catch ya later
嗨  章鱼哥
Hi, Squidward
要来玩吗
Wanna play?
不要
No
离我远一点
And leave me alone
好吧  章鱼哥
OK, Squidward
再见
see ya later
空白的画布
The blank canvas
蕴含无限的可能
Infinite possibilities
已知与未知宇宙里所有的色彩
All the colors of the known and unknown universe
都藏在我的调色盘里
hiding on my palette
艺术家上前  准备开始创作
The artiste approaches, ready to create
章鱼哥  要来玩吗
Hey, Squidward, wanna play?
不要
好吧  章鱼哥
OK, Squidward
再见
see ya later
也许可以在书中的世界探寻幽静
Perhaps I can find solitude in the printed word
章鱼哥  要来玩吗
Hey, Squidward, wanna play?
第七卷
好吧  章鱼哥
OK, Squidward
再见
see ya later
什么
What?
嗨  章鱼哥
Hi, Squidward
要来玩捉迷藏吗
Wanna play hide and seek?
好  海绵宝宝
OK, SpongeBob
你先藏
You hide first
不会吧  他跑哪去了
Oh, no, where'd he go?
看来他赢了
I guess he wins
失败的味道从来没这么美好过
Defeat has never tasted so sweet
喂
Yello?
要不要来玩猜字吊吊乐
How about a game of hangman?
[ 一人选词一人猜字母，猜错一次
则画一笔上吊小人，画完或猜对则结束 ]
要不要来玩挂电话
How about a game of hang up?
看来没法再悠闲下去了
I guess this brings an end to my luxuriating
要不要玩鸭鸭寄居蟹
How 'bout duck, duck hermit crab?
[ 改自duck duck goose，规则类似丢手绢 ]
跳房子
Hopscotch?
章鱼哥说你来做
Squidward says?
偷培根
Steal the bacon?
[ 一队在未被另一队触杀的情况下
抢走场上的旗子或其他物品 ]
沉睡海狮子
Sleeping sea lions?
[ 改自sleeping lions
“狮子”装睡，“猎人”逗醒“狮子” ]
鲨鱼抓小鱼
Sharks and minnows?
击沉潜艇
Sink the submarine?
纸牌
Kings and queens?
麻将
Mahjong?
我从来没玩过这游戏
I've never played this game before
叫什么名字
What's it called?
名字叫
It's called
我绝对不跟你玩
I will never play with you
永远都不
Ever
莫名感觉
Something tells me
章鱼哥今天不想玩
that Squidward doesn't want to play today
有了
That's it
既然没法跟真正的章鱼哥玩
If I can't play with the real Squidward
那我就自己做一个
I'll just make one of my own
那个白痴总算开窍了
I think that moron finally gets it
我可不想再看到他或者听到他在
I don't want to see or hear him for the
海绵宝宝  能不能别吵了
SpongeBob, will you make that racket stop
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
你马上给我开
You open this door right this
你好啊  章鱼哥
"Hello Squidward"
章鱼哥  是我
"Squidward, it's me
小小章鱼哥
mini Squidward"
你在干什么  海绵宝宝
What are you doing SpongeBob?
你好啊  章鱼哥
Hello, Squidward
你又想怎么烦我
What manner of annoying scheme is this?
跟他打声招呼  章鱼哥
Just say hello to him, Squidward
他可敏感了
You know how sensitive he is
嗨
Hi
海绵宝宝  怎么
Now SpongeBob, what the
章鱼哥
Squidward?
他比较喜欢别人直呼全名
He prefers to be addressed by his full name
你好啊  章鱼哥
Hello, Squidward
天气很好吧  章鱼哥老兄弟
Wondrous weather we're having, eh, Squidward, old pal?
海绵宝宝  你这是什么意思
SpongeBob, what is the meaning of this?
海绵宝宝做了替身版的你  也就是我
SpongeBob made a replacement you, me
这样你本尊不想玩的时候
So that when you you don't want to play
海绵宝宝就能跟我这个替身玩了
SpongeBob can play with me, you
所以说你可以顶替我
So, you'll be filling in for me
陪海绵宝宝玩他的笨游戏吗
when SpongeBob wants to play one of his stupid games?
对
Yeah?
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you, thank you
三个词
Three words
电影名
Movie title
十二怒水母
12 angry jellyfish
[ 改自《十二怒汉》 ]
他怎么猜到的
How does he do it?
小小章鱼哥       我
又猜对了  小小章
Right again, squidy
你可真是个猜谜大师
You little charades master, you
章鱼哥  你长得有点不一样了
Squidward, you look a little different
你最近在健身吗
Have you been working out?
派大星  其实这是
Actually Patrick, this is
你等下  海绵宝宝
Hold it, SpongeBob
想到了
I know
你刮了胡子
You shaved your beard
蟹堡王
好了
All right, now
谁点了蟹  黄堡
Who has the Krabby Patty
还有谁点了蟹黄  堡
and who has the Krabby Patty?
看吧
See?
因为这俩都是
'Cause they're both
蟹黄堡
Krabby
真好笑  小小章鱼哥
Good one, mini Squidward
你永远都是个开心果
You are always a ray of sunshine
准备好来迎接
Are you ready
蟹堡王又一个美好的工作日了没
for another fabulous day of work at the Krusty Krab?
那当然了
Of course I am
我爱工作
I love to work
海绵宝宝手上的那个小家伙是谁
Who is that little fella with SpongeBob?
不知道  但他好帅啊
I don't know, but isn't he handsome?
对  他可真帅
Yeah, he is handsome
抱歉先生  我能为你点餐吗
Sorry sir, can I take your order?
我可不喜欢你的态度  小弟
No, I don't like your attitude, bub
原来这就是蟹堡王所谓的友好服务吗
Is this what the Krusty Krab calls friendly service?
抱歉先生  我能为你点餐吗
Sorry sir, can I take your order?
这还差不多
Now that's more like it
总算有个态度友好的服务生了
Finally, a server with a good attitude
非常感谢你
Well, thank you very much
你们这边最好的蟹黄堡来八打
I'll take eight dozen of your finest patties, please
别让那个傻子碰到
Don't let ol' chowder pants touch 'em
他多半会玷污了蟹黄堡
He might taint the patties
好  全给你干
Fine then, go ahead
替我干活
Do my work for me
我倒要开始喜欢上这位小小章鱼哥了
I'm startin' to like this mini Squidward
替我干活  省得让海绵宝宝来烦我
Doing my work, keeping SpongeBob off my back
轻轻松松就能习惯
I could get used to this
上菜了  小小章鱼哥
Order up, mini squid
好的  海绵宝宝
Ok, SpongeBob
我很乐意帮忙
always happy to help
给你吧  兄弟
Here ya go, pal
加油干
Go get 'em, tiger
好
Ok
是谁点了蟹  黄堡
Now, who had the Krabby Patty
还有谁点了蟹黄  堡呢
and who had the Krabby Patty?
怎么
What the
那可是我想的笑话
that's my joke
亲爱的
Honey
这个新来的小小章鱼哥可真幽默
This new mini Squidward is such a card
而且服务也周到  亲爱的
And a great waiter, dear
没错
You're right
比那个老古板的大号章鱼哥强多了
So much better
than that old, lousy, larger-scale Squidward
没错
Yeah
让那个小家伙过来
Bring that little fella over here
我要给他300块的小费
and let me give him a $300 tip
什么
What?
好了好了
All right, all right
都够了
That's enough
我休息完了
My break is finished
好耶  我又来上班了
Oh, boy, back to work
先等一下
Hold on a second there
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
章鱼哥  我的头足类动物
Squidward, me cephalopod
很遗憾要告诉你这件事
I'm sorry to tell you this
其实也没那么遗憾
Well, not that sorry
我的客人更喜欢新来的小小章鱼哥
Me customers prefer the new smaller Squidward
不喜欢你
to you
我也一样
And so do I
因为他帮我赚到了钱
'Cause he's making me some bucks
我要把你的职务改成勤杂工
I'm changing your job to busboy
即刻生效
effective immediately
安静点  看人家怎么干
Now pipe down and watch how it's done
大家看
Hey, everybody
我是章鱼哥  我爱跳舞
I'm Squidward and I love to dance
我喜欢边吃饭边看跳舞
I for one love to watch people dance while I eat
谁跟我一样
Who's with me?
谁想要小小章鱼哥跳舞助助兴
Who wants mini Squidward to dance for our amusement?
天啊  好吧
Well, gosh, OK
哪了不起了
What's the big deal?
那些都是我的舞步
Those are all my moves
哒哒
Ta-da
真是没一点才华
Talk about no talent
也许章鱼哥得做个缩小手术
Maybe Squidward should get size reduction surgery
这样才能跳得好一点
so he'll dance better
那个小小章鱼哥
That mini squid
大家一起跳
Everybody dance
太可恶了
That was awful
他偷了我的笑话
He stole my jokes
他偷了我的工作
He stole my job
他偷了我的欢呼和掌声
He stole my standing ovation
你个榆木脑袋
You little wooden fiend
别再偷我的大好生活了
Stop stealing my life
住手  住手
Stop, stop
求你别咬我新客户的脑袋
Don't gnaw on the head of my new client, please
你不知道你这是在做什么
You don't know what you're doing
你疯了吗
Are you mad?
饶了它吧
Have mercy
等一下
Wait a minute
我先前见过你
I've seen you before
你是个音乐经纪人
You're that music agent
给我最爱的竖笛乐手做经纪的那位
that represents my favorite clarinet player
你好  我是迈罗J芬克尔鱼
Salutations, I'm Milo J Finkerfish
卷泡唱片的人才管理
Talent manager for curly bubbles records
所以你是来跟我签合约做唱片的吗
You mean you're here to sign me for a record deal?
我对此的回答是  免谈
The answer to that question is a big n-o
反而这位小家伙才是好得呱呱叫
This little fella on the other hand
is woo-hoo, woo-hoo, good
我们要让他签订百万元合约
We're offering him a million-dollar contract
合约
附赠一套亮片装
and a sequined suit
亮片装
A sequined suit
那才是我应得的待遇
That's what you're supposed to offer me
与其带走个劣质冒牌货
Why take a cheap knock-off
不如来找原版得了
when you can have the original
要在哪签订
Now where do I sign?
你小子想得美
Yeah, right, kid
小小章鱼哥  我们的情谊到此为止了
Well, ol' mini Squidward, I guess this is it
我们曾经猜谜玩得多开心
We've had some good times playing charades
又像两只轻盈的蝴蝶一样快乐共舞
and dancing around like two giddy butterflies
记得吗
Remember?
往日时光真美好
Yeah, those were the days
但现在你也是时候要继续前进了
But I guess it's time for you to move on, huh?
迈向更美好的前景
On to greener pastures
永别了  老友
Arrivederci, mon frere
好了小子  来轰动全场吧
All right kid, let's go become a sensation
我们蛤莱美奖见
And we'll see you at the clammy awards
不对  到时多半见不到你
Oh, no, I guess I won't
拜拜
Buh-bye
怎么了  真实大小的章鱼哥
What's the matter, actual size Squidward?
我的梦想破灭了
My dreams are crushed
不过呢
But, hey
起码再也不用见到那个小小章鱼哥了
At least I won't have to see that mini squid ever again
对啊  我还有更好的东西呢
Yeah, I have something even better
另外一个我
Another me